joomlage.com 2019-03-20

# Privacy Policy

The following article sets out how we handle your personal identifiable information if you’re a Joomlage.com user or visitor to our site. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for Joomlage.com and it is important to us that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information. 

By using the Joomlage.com website, or using any Joomlage.com products/services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy (last updated on May 26th, 2018) 

###  What personal information do we collect from you when visiting our website? 

**Personal Information:** At the time of registration a user will be requested to submit the following information: full name, email address, username, a valid password, registration date, last visit date, purchase history, and IP address. Joomlage.com only asks you to disclose as much information as is necessary to provide you with service requested by you or to submit a question/suggestion/comment in relation to our website. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

**Payment Information:** When you provide your payment information, it's directly transmitted to our payment processors, PayPal, Stripe or 2Checkout. They use and process your payment information in accordance with their privacy policy. We at no point store your payment information. 

**Anonymous Information:** We may also collect details of your visits to our site (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data), and the resources that you access. When you access our website, your computer’s browser provides us with information such as your IP address, browser type, access time and referring URL which is collected and used to compile statistical data on the use of our website. This information may be used to help us to improve our site and the services we offer. 

###  What purposes your data are used for? 

With the data stored on our site, we identify you as our customer/subscriber/patron and deliver products/notices and other marketing materials. As a visitor, you aren’t allowed to purchase any product or subscribe to newsletter or make a comment anonymously. So, these data are the only means to identify you and allow you to make these actions on our site. 

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. You will occasionally receive newsletters regarding new products, services, coupons and promotions provided by Joomlage.com. 

###  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

###  How long do we retain your information? 

Information collected when you register with Joomlage.com or subscribe to Joomlage.com services is retained for as long you do not delete the account. 

###  What policy do we have for children’s personal information? 

Joomlage.com does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our Service. If we obtain actual knowledge that any personal information about a child under the age of 13 was collected, that information will be immediately removed without any notice. By using this site, you agree that you are at least 13 years old. 

###  How you can review, update, get a copy or delete your data? 

At any point you can review and update your personal information stored directly through our site. To review or edit your information, login to our site and navigate to ‘My Profile’. If you want to delete your information, send an email to [info@joomlage.com](mailto:info@Joomlage.com.com) including your Joomlage.com username and we will do so with immediate effect.
